tigermist.com.au 2019-03-04

# Privacy - Tiger Mist

**Our  Protection Of Your Privacy**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of any information provided by you as our customer and will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or unauthorised access.

In dealing with your personal information as a customer, we will fulfill all obligations applicable to us by law. 

From time to time it may be necessary for us to revise and update our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time without prior notice by updating this page. We suggest you familiarise yourself regularly with our policies and your rights before placing an order with us to ensure you are aware of our most up to date privacy policy. 

**Details We  Collect From You**

There is some information we, and the third party providers we engage, will collect from you when you visit our site or get in touch with us. This includes:

  * Your name, email address, contact number, billing and delivery address 
  * Information about your device and browser
  * Demographic information such as your location 
  * Your IP address
  * Pages you visit on our site and products you view

**Cookies**

We also use browser cookies to recognise you when you return to our site after your first visit. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your computer's browser and are created when you use your browser to visit a website that uses cookies to keep track of your movements within the site. Cookies are helpful for your return visits to a site as they remember your login, preferences, and other personalised functions. 

We use cookies to measure website traffic, on-site behaviour for the purposes of marketing and make your on-site experience as relevant to you as possible. You can at any time disable this feature on your browser if you do not want your website activity to be identified as your own, however this may limit your use of some features on our site.

**Our Use Of Your Information**

We will not sell or distribute your information to third parties unless we have your express consent to do so or are required to by law. The information we collect from you is used for the purposes of:

  * Processing, fulfilling and delivering an order to you
  * Responding to an enquiry you submit to us via our customer service channels
  * Sending you email correspondence via our newsletter (if you have opted into this)
  * Business analysis, reporting and market research;
  * Improving our products and services. 

We partner with third parties to manage our payments, advertising, marketing and email marketing. Some of your personal information is processed by these third parties on our behalf. This means that some of your data is hosted outside of Australia (where we are located) and the European Economic Area. When opting into receiving communication from us or by placing an order with us via any of our platforms, we take this to mean that you have read our privacy policy and all terms, and that you consent to the use and storage of your information as mentioned in this policy.

Further, when you subscribe to our database and provide us with your personal information, you consent to our use of your personal information, such as your name, email address and phone number for marketing purposes. This includes, but is not limited to, sending you correspondence such as newsletters, competitions and promotions via email, SMS, social media and postal mail. 

**Opting Out**

You can opt out of receiving any opt-in communications from us at any time by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of every email we send you from our mailing list (this does not include emails relating to your order or any customer queries you send us via our customer service channels) or SMS 'STOP' to opt-out of our mobile marketing list. You can opt out of any marketing displayed to you via social media platforms such as Facebook or search engines like Google by amending your settings to exclude marketing activity via its channels. 

Further, we store your data for as long as your account with us remains active or for as long as we need to provide you services or as required by law.  

**Contacting Us**

Your data protection is extremely important to us and we make all reasonable efforts to protect this. We ensure that internal processes are strictly followed and access to your data is as limited as possible. Our website and your connection to it is also secure.

If you believe any information we have of yours is incorrect or have any queries about our privacy policy or terms of use, please contact us at your earliest convenience via email at customercare@tigermist.com.au or phone on (03) 8418 0046 between 8am and 4pm AEST (we are based in Melbourne, Australia). For all physical mail, our mailing address is PO Box 566 Richmond Victoria 3121.
